[Music]
Welcome. In this session, we'll talk
about uh user experience improvements in
this wave. We have several areas to talk
about. We'll talk about improvements
related to handling screen state and
handling your windows and pages. We have
a new advanced tellme feature that I
would like to show uh to you and we have
some improvements related to copilot and
agents. So let's uh dive in.
We'll start with uh improvements related
to to screen and that uh shows you how
you can handle your uh your workspace.
Uh let's let's see it in a demo. So you
will notice in business central
the user interface changes when you open
and close the factbox.
That's right now becomes a default
behavior. You can of course resize the
factbox but now you can also resize the
copilot pane and also the help pane and
page scripting pane. All of those
improvements are right now enabled by
default.
Another feature that I would like to
talk to you is the advanced tellme which
adds an ability to find pages in reports
uh much faster and again uh the best way
to show it to you uh is in a demo. This
feature is in preview. So you need to
enable that in feature management. But
when you do that and you go and try to
find products
for instance in RO explorer you see this
try advanced preview because we didn't
find anything about products. Actually
we have a page that uh talks about
products and which is called in business
central items. Uh and advanced tell me
is able to find it very quickly.
Advanced tell me is also available if
you go through tell me um option here or
press alt q and then switch to uh
advanced tell me
and then uh search in this way. This
uses semantic search to determine which
pages or reports are closer to the
search term that you entered in Teli.
And then uh next group of features
relate uh to copilot and agent.
Everything that we uh do in the user
experience related to uh copilot and AI
agentic imp features in business
central. Uh I will show you a quick demo
of one of those.
So you will notice that I have a sales
order agent running and sales order
agent requires my assistance.
I have a request from a customer to add
procure
in yellow but the agent is not able to
find those uh those that kind of
product.
In here we have now the ability to give
additional instructions to the agent
either by selecting a predefined option
or providing uh text instructions. So I
can say take Berlin
chair
and confirm.
It makes it much easier to operate and
talk to your agent.
And we have some other features to talk
to you about. Um as you see on the
screen, we have several new
improvements. Let me show you some of
them in action.
We added an option to show weak numbers
in date picker. You will see that in
every date picker right now when you
press shift home you can see the week
numbers here on the side and of course
we can you can toggle that pressing
shift home again and this of course
follows regional settings for your user.
We are also introducing an option to
mask some information and hide that
information from screen that is uh
needed for for fields that might be
sensitive. As you can see here, the bank
account number for your company is
currently hidden and I can reveal the
data. If I press this little button
here, you will see this feature showing
up in different areas of Business
Central in the coming uh releases. And
you as an AL developer can also use that
property to uh decorate your your
fields.
This feature is also in preview. So you
have to enable that in feature
management. Uh here
great you have learned about all the
usability improvements in Business
Central in this wave. There's plenty of
various other resources and links to
have a look at. Uh, I would encourage
you to to try and submit ideas for new
improvements you would like to see in
the product in the in the next releases.
And of course, follow us on LinkedIn,
watch our our videos on YouTube, and
more. Thank you very much.